

Obaida Al-Naheel

WEB DEVELOPER

- Lattakia Syria
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/obaida28/
- https://obaida28.github.io/
- https://github.com/obaida28
- +963 998354543

PROFILE

I have four years of experience as a back-end web developer in ASP, C#, and SQL.

I enjoy problem solving and coming up with solutions. I want to boost my skills. I try my best not to abandon tasks until they are completed perfectly. I happily share my knowledge and experience, assisting others, and exchanging ideas.

SKILLS

- Back-end: C#, SQL Server, Asp.Net, .Net MVC, .Net Core,.Net Web forms,.Net Web Services API.
- Front-end: HTML, CSS, JavaScript,React.js.
- Soft Skills: problem solving, teamwork, communication skills, creativity, work ethic.
- . UML

LANGUAGES

- Arabic Native Language
- · English Intermediate

EDUCATION

Tishreen University

Sep 2015 - Present

- Bachelor of Computer Science, Minor: Software Engineering.
- Activities: SCPC Programming Competition 2018 & 2019.
- Projects:
 - X-ray Clinic: Includes a landing page and dashboard for a clinic where patients can book appointments from the home page and doctors can organize their schedules, save patient information, and use AI to diagnose diseases - 2022.
 - Movies Library: PHP and MySQL 2022.
 - Team Management System: allows you to create projects and tasks, then assign them to people, Django/Python - 2022.
 - Cars Store: Allow people to buy and sell cars, as well as hold auctions, using Asp.net MVC - 2021.
 - Task Demo: Organize and Schedule Tasks, using Java swing and SQLite - 2017.

EXPERIENCE

Emenu Aug 2023- Now

• I begin as a back-end developer intern using ASP.NET Core.

Robotic Mind

Sep 2018 - Jan 2023

- I Begin as a back-end web developer using C#, SQL, and ASP.NET Web Forms.
- I improved my front-end skills, particularly JavaScript.
- I discovered innovative solutions to maintaining clean code.
- I created Algorithms to solve problems and create new features.
- · I learned about API and authentication.
- I learned about project planning, from gathering to analyzing, designing, and implementing.
- I was promoted to team supervisor.
- · I learned WordPress Control Managment System.
- I started improving my skills in the .Net field.
- . Activities: Zahr Nisan Exhibition.
- · Projects:
 - Al-Basheer Iraq: E-Commerce System for car parts store.
 - Amal Academy: portfolio and control panel for customizing products and courses on the landing page.
 - Marten Do: it is a service company, we provide them with a dashboard that allows them to receive, manage, and monitor their orders.
 - Robotic Mind Accounting Software: for Zahr Nisan Exhibition 2019.